Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Communist and Socialist Serials TAM.747
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: American Publications, 1881-2010; 68.4 Linear Feet in 89 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript boxes, and 102 flat boxes
  - Monsters of All Kinds Can be Destroyed: Revolutionary Union, Reading, PA, circa 1960s; cuid12276 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - The "New Economic Policy": Revolutionary Union, Philadelphia, PA, circa 1970s; cuid12277 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Revolution: Revolutionary Union/Revolutionary Communist Party, Chicago, IL, circa 1973-2015; cuid12278 (Box 59, Folder 1-6, Box 56, Folder 13, Box 60, Folder 1-4, Box 61, Box 62, Folder 1-5)
  - The Communist Party: A Manual on Organization: Revolutionary Union/Workers Library Publishers, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12279 (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - Movin' On!: Revolutionary Workers Congress, Detroit, MI, 1975; cuid12280 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Fighting Worker: Publication of the Revolutionary Workers Group: Revolutionary Workers Group, Detroit, MI, 1983; cuid12281 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Workers' Truth: Revolutionary Workers Group, Chicago, IL, 1973-1975; cuid12282 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Worker: Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, Chicago, IL, 1978; cuid12283 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Workers Voice/Voz del Obrero: Revolutionary Workers Headquarters, Chicago, IL, 1978-1980; cuid12284 (Box 121, Folder 3, Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Barricades in Barcelona: Revolutionary Workers League, Chicago, IL, 1937; cuid12285 (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - Draft Program of the Revolutionary Workers League: Revolutionary Workers League, Chicago, IL, 1939; cuid12286 (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Shall Workers Support a Labor Party?: Revolutionary Workers League, 1938; cuid12287 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - Workers Struggle: Revolutionary Workers League, Detroit, MI, 1981-1982; cuid12288 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Fourth International: Revolutionary Workers League of the U.S., Chicago, IL, 1937; cuid12289 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Lenin and the Bolsheviki: Revolutionary Workers League of the U.S., 1936; cuid12290 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - Workers' Revolution or Wars Foreer: Revolutionary Workers League U.S.A., Chicago, IL, 1945; cuid12291 (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - If This Be Treason: Revolutionary Workers League U.S.A./ Central Committee of the Revolutionary Workers League, Cleveland, OH, 1949; cuid12292 (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Worker in the 1940 Elections: Revolutionary Workers League U.S.A./Demos Press, Chicago, IL, cuid12293 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Lessons on the Road to the New Communist (4th) International: Revolutionary Workers League, U.S., Chicago, IL, 1904; cuid12294 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Dialectical Materialism: Revolutionary Workers League/ Demos Press, Chicago, IL, 1941; cuid12295 (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Fight Fascism - Defend Revolutionists in Spain: Revolutionary Workers League/ Demos Press, Chicago, IL, 1938; cuid12296 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Program of the Revolutionary Workers League U.S.A.: Revolutionary Workers League/ Demos Press, Chicago, IL, 1939; cuid12297 (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Red Flag: Revolutionary Workers' Party (Trotskyist), British Section, IVth International, 1967-1968; cuid12298 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - El Combatiente: Revolutionary Workers Party/ Organo del Partido Revolucionario de los Trabajadores, 1974; cuid12299 (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - Revolutionary Youth: Revolutionary Youth League, New York, NY, 1978; cuid12300 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Our Struggle = Nuestra Lucha: Ricardo Chavez-Ortiz Defense Committee, Los Angeles, CA, circa 1970s; cuid12301 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - International Labour Movement: RILU, 1928-1929; cuid12302 (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Social Economic Review: RILU, 1929, 1931; cuid12303 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Fight for the Fourth International: Robert Williams, 1937; cuid12304 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Poland, 1970-71: Workers vs State: Root & Branch, Cambridge, MA, 1971; cuid12305 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - "I Accuse!": Roy Defense Committee of India, New York, NY, 1932; cuid12306 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Internal Bulletin: RSL, 1940; cuid12307 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Organizer's Report: RSL, 1981; cuid12308 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Russian State Party Newsletter: Russian State Party/ Ruth Fischer, New York, NY, 1946; cuid12309 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Common Sense: San Francisco Socialist Coalition, San Francisco, CA, 1973-1975; cuid12310 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Sanders Scoop: Sanders for Congress, Burlington, VT, 1998; cuid12311 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Action Newsletter: Baltimore, MD, circa 1980s; cuid12312 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Studies in Comparative Communism: School of Politics and International Relations, University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA, 1968; cuid12313 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Transition from Feudalism to Capitalism: A Symposium: Science & Society/ Kenion Press, New York, NY, 1954; cuid12314 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Jones Family's Grandchildren: SDS, Norman, OK, 1968; cuid12315 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Vanguard: SDS, Fullerton, CA, 1970; cuid12316 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin Interieur du Secretariat International de la IVe Internationale: Secretariat International de la IVe Internationale, 1954; cuid12317 (Box 37, Folder 0)
  - Service d'information et de presse: Secretariat International pour la Quatrieme Internationale, 1935-1937; cuid12318 (Box 136, Folder 4, Box 242, Folder 9)
  - From the Left: Section on Marxist Sociology, American Sociological Association, 2003-2004; cuid12319 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - SD Papers: Social Demcorats, New York, NY, 1977, 1979, 1985; cuid12320 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Party-Social Democratic Federation Proceedings: social democratic federation, Detroit, MI, 1958; cuid12321 (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Appeal to Reason: Social Democrats, USA, San Francisco, CA, 1974-1988; cuid12322 (Box 121, Folder 7-8)
  - The Heritage of Debs: The Fight Against the War: Social Party, USA, Chicago, IL, 1935; cuid12323 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Russia Turns East: Social Science Publishers, 1926; cuid12324 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Speech of Unity: "Socialism of the XXI Century" Publications, 2007; cuid11442 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - In Defense of Revolutionary Continuity: Socialist Action, 1983; cuid12325 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Socalist Action Information Bulletin (v1-6): Socialist Action, San Francisco, CA, 1984; cuid12326 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Action: Socialist Action, San Francisco, CA, 1983-1984, 1986; cuid12327 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Action Internal Information Bulletin: Socialist Action, San Francisco, CA, 1984, 1988, 1991; cuid12328 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Justice: Socialist Alternative, Long Island City, NY/Seattle, WA, 1997-1998, 2006; cuid12329 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Cadre: Socialist Cadre, Detroit, MI, circa 1970s; cuid12330 (Box 168, Folder 30)
  - Socialist: Socialist Educational Society, New York, NY, 1929-1930; cuid12331 (Box 168, Folder 31)
  - Friedrich Adler: Socialist International Information, 1952; cuid12332 (Box 168, Folder 32)
  - Crisis: Socialist Labor Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1971-1972; cuid12333 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Perspectives: Socialist Labor Committee, Brooklyn, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12334 (Box 168, Folder 33)
  - Marx on Mallock -or- Facts vs. Fiction: Socialist Labor Party, New York, NY, 1908; cuid12335 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - National Executive Committee: Socialist Labor Party, 1949; cuid12336 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Studies: Socialist Labor Party, Palo Alto, CA, 1900; cuid12337 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - What is Socialism: Socialist Labor Party, 1954; cuid12338 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Fifty Years of American Marxism: Socialist Labor Party of America, New York, NY, 1941; cuid12339 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Weekly People: Socialist Labor Party of America, New York, NY, 1935, 1938, 1959-1960, 1967, 1972-1973, 1976; cuid12340 (Box 40, Folder 1-4, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 19)
  - International Bulletin: Socialist League, San Francisco, CA, 1976; cuid12341 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Labor News: Socialist League, San Francisco, CA, 1978-1979; cuid12342 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Workers' Power: Socialist League, San Francisco, CA, 1971; cuid12343 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Organizer: Socialist Organizer, San Francisco, CA, 1991-1992; cuid12344 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Organizer: Building the Labor Party and a Worker's International: Socialist Organizer, the U.S. Fraternal Section of the Fourth International, San Francisco, CA, 2004-2006; cuid12345 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Notes from Orange?: Socialist Organizing Committee, Santa Ana, CA, 1977; cuid12346 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Are These The Only Choices I've Got: Socialist Party, Milwaukee, WI, 1984; cuid12347 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin: Socialist Party, 1943; cuid12348 (Box 169, Folder 33)
  - New Leader: Socialist Party, New York, NY, 1932; cuid12349 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Platform: Socialist Party, New York, NY, 1952; cuid12350 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - The Truth About Socialism: Socialist Party, New York, NY, 1943; cuid12351 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - West Side Socialist News: Socialist Party, New York, NY, 1931; cuid12352 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Special Bulletin: Socialist Party (Max Delson), New York, NY, 1935; cuid12353 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - American Socialist Quarterly Reprints: Socialist Party of America, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12354 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Eighteenth National Convention of the Socialist Party of America: Socialist Party of America, Chicago, IL, 1934; cuid12355 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Fulcrum: Socialist Party of Canada, 1980; cuid12356 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Yankee Radical (leaflet): Socialist Party of Massachusetts, Boston, MA, 1970; cuid12357 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Metro Newsletter: Socialist Party of New Jersey, Saddle Brook, NJ, 1996; cuid12358 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Real Democracy: Socialist Party of New Jersey, Hoboken, NJ, 1997; cuid12359 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Activist: Socialist Party of New Jersey (SPUSA), Upper Montclair, NJ, 2010; cuid12360 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - Newsletter of the Socialist Party of New York State: Socialist Party of New York State, Syracuse, NY, 1982; cuid12361 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Socialist Party of New York State: Socialist Party of New York State, Syracuse, NY, 1983; cuid12362 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - Radical Politics: Socialist Party of Rhode Island, Providence, RI, 1967; cuid12363 (Box 169, Folder 18)
  - Political Guide for the Workers: Socialist Party of the United States, Chicago, IL, 1920; cuid12364 (Box 169, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Action: Socialist Party of the United States of America, Chicago, IL, 1935-1936; cuid12365 (Box 120, Folder 8, Box 223, Folder 18)
  - Socialist Party 35th Anniversary Journal: Socialist Party of the United States of America, Chicago, IL, 1936; cuid12366 (Box 169, Folder 20, Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Smash the War System!: Socialist Party of the USA, Chicago, IL, 1938; cuid12367 (Box 169, Folder 21)
  - Socialist Party: Socialist Party of the USA, Chicago, IL, 1936; cuid12368 (Box 169, Folder 22)
  - Northwest Call Newsletter: Socialist Party of Washington, Seattle, WA, circa 1960s; cuid12369 (Box 169, Folder 23)
  - A Lot of What's Best in America...Is Socialist: Socialist Party USA, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12370 (Box 169, Folder 24)
  - A Socialist Perspective on Reproductive Rights: Socialist Party USA, New York, NY, 1988; cuid12371 (Box 169, Folder 25)
  - For a Liveable Future: Socialist Party USA, Los Angeles, CA, 1988; cuid12372 (Box 169, Folder 26)
  - March of Socialism - 1928-1932 - Journal of the Seventeenth National Convention: Socialist Party USA, Milwaukee, WI, cuid12373 (Box 169, Folder 27)
  - Torch: Socialist Party USA, New York, NY, 1989-1991; cuid12374 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Rhode Island Red: Socialist Party USA, Rhode Island State Committee, Providence, RI, 1981; cuid12375 (Box 169, Folder 28)
  - Brooklyn Socialist: Socialist Party, Kings Co., Brooklyn, NY, 1911; cuid12376 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - Plan for America: Socialist Party, USA, New York, NY, 1949; cuid12377 (Box 169, Folder 30)
  - Socialist Handbook 1937: Socialist Party, USA, Chicago, IL, cuid12378 (Box 169, Folder 31)
  - Socialist Party, USA: 1970 Convention Minutes: Socialist Party, USA, New York, NY, cuid12379 (Box 169, Folder 32)
  - Socialist Bulletin: Socialist Party-Social Democratic Federation, New York, NY, 1958; cuid12380 (Box 169, Folder 29)
  - Soviet-American Review: Socialist Political-Economic Survey, Chicago, IL, 1990; cuid12381 (Box 169, Folder 34)
  - Class of Struggle: Socialist Publication Society, New York, NY, 1918; cuid12382 (Box 103, Folder 27)
  - Socialist: Socialist publishing Company, New Haven, CT, 1911; cuid12383 (Box 169, Folder 35)
  - On Learning from History: Socialist Revolution, San Francisco, CA, circa 1960s; cuid12384 (Box 169, Folder 36)
  - Socialist Tribune: Socialist Tribune, Inc., Milwaukee, WI, 1976-1979; cuid12385 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - [Resolution of the Socialist Union (Britain)]: Socialist Union-(Internationalist), New York, NY, 1974; cuid12386 (Box 162, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Workers voters pamphlets: Socialist Workers, New York, NY, 1965; cuid12387 (Box 169, Folder 37)
  - Workers Review: Socialist Workers Group, 1953; cuid12388 (Box 162, Folder 15)
  - Bill of Rights for working people: Socialist Workers national compaign committee, Washington, DC, 1976; cuid12389 (Box 169, Folder 38)
  - America's Permanent Depression: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1976; cuid12390 (Box 169, Folder 39)
  - Bulletin: Socialist Workers Party, 1980-1981 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Bulletin on the French Situation #s 1 and 2: Socialist Workers Party, 1938; cuid12391 (Box 169, Folder 40)
  - Declaration of Principles and Constitution of the Socialist Workers Party: Socialist Workers Party, 1938; cuid12392 (Box 169, Folder 41)
  - Education Bulletin: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1948; cuid12393 (Box 169, Folder 42, Box 223, Folder 15, Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Healy "Reconstructs" the Fourth international: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1966; cuid12394 (Box 169, Folder 43)
  - How to Fight War: Socialist Workers Party, circa 1950s; cuid12395 (Box 169, Folder 44)
  - Militant Steelworker: Socialist Workers Party, Buffalo, NY, 1958; cuid12396 (Box 169, Folder 45)
  - Open the Doors: Socialist Workers Party, 1938; cuid12397 (Box 169, Folder 46)
  - Party Organizer: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1978-1981, 1984-1985; cuid12398 (Box 170, Folder 1-4, Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Self Determination for Palestine: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12399 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Workers Party Bulletin: Socialist Workers Party, 1978; cuid12400 (Box 160, Folder 11, Box 242, Folder 5-6)
  - SWP discussion bulletin: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1967, 1971; cuid12401 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - These of Revolutionary Socialists on the Jewish Problem: Socialist Workers Party, New York, NY, 1944; cuid12402 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Workers Voice: Socialist Workers Party, New Jersey, 1937; cuid12403 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Constitution of the S.W.P.: Socialist Workers Party - National Education Department, 1946; cuid12404 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Twilight of the British Empire: Socialist Workers Party - New York Local, New York, NY, 1938; cuid12405 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - How to Fight War: Socialist Workers Party & Young Peoples Socialist League, Newark, NJ, circa 1960s; cuid12406 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Workers' Voice: Socialist Workers Party Lenin Branch, Newark, NJ, 1938; cuid12407 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Lima Conference: Socialist Workers Party, National Education Department, 1939; cuid12408 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - National Communication: Socialist Youth League, 1952; cuid12409 (Box 160, Folder 18, Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Sing!: Socialist Youth League, New York, NY, circa 1960s; cuid12410 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Youth League Newsletter: Socialist Youth League, Chicago, IL, circa 1960s; cuid12411 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - Socialist Youth League Report: Socialist Youth League, Newark, NJ, 1949; cuid12412 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - SYL Newsletter: Socialist Youth League, 1953; cuid12413 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - Young Socialist Partisan: Socialist Youth League, Newark, NJ, circa 1950s; cuid12414 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - Calendar: Socialist Youth League Buro, 1946; cuid12415 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - The United Front Against Imperialism?: Sojourner Truth Organization, Chicago, IL, 1972; cuid12416 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Solidarity: Socialist-Feminism: Solidarity, Somerville, MA, 1981; cuid12417 (Box 160, Folder 26)
  - Solidarity Newsletter: Solidarity Newsletter, Detroit, MI, 1986; cuid12418 (Box 160, Folder 27)
  - The Rape of Vietnam: Solidarity Pamphlelt, Philadelphia, PA, circa 1970; cuid12419 (Box 160, Folder 28)
  - Solidarity Update: Solidarity Update, Berkeley, CA, 1983; cuid12420 (Box 160, Folder 29)
  - Spark: South Work SPARK, Chicago, IL, 1979-1980; cuid12421 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Behind the Cotton Curtain: Southern Democratic Socialists, Moss Point, MS, 1982; cuid12422 (Box 160, Folder 30)
  - Southern People's Common Program for Democracy, Prosperity and Peace: Southern Regional Committee of the Communist Party, USA, New York, NY, 1953; cuid12423 (Box 160, Folder 31)
  - The Soviet White Paper on the North Atlantic Pact: Soviet Russia Today, New York, NY, 1949; cuid12424 (Box 160, Folder 32)
  - Soviet Union Review: Soviet Union Information Bureau, Washington, DC, 1930, 1932; cuid12425 (Box 160, Folder 33)
  - Sozialistische Arbeiterzeitung: Sozialistischen Arbeitergruppe (SAG), 1978; cuid12426 (Box 160, Folder 34)
  - Terrorzentrale: Sozialistisches Arbeitskollektiv Jura, circa 1970s; cuid12427 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Class Struggle: SPARK, Chicago, IL, 2001-2003; cuid12428 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Internal Discussion Bulletin: Spartacist, New York, NY, 1975; cuid12429 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Marxist Studies: Spartacist, New York, NY, 1969; cuid12430 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Workers Vanguard - 'Class Struggles in Auto': Spartacist, New York, NY, 1973; cuid12431 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Spartacist League Split: Spartacist League, 1968; cuid12432 (Box 161, Folder 4, Box 242, Folder 16)
  - Workers Hammer: Spartacist League, 1992; cuid12433 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Black History and the Class Struggle: Spartacist Publishing Co., New York, NY, 1998, 2001; cuid12434 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Cuadernos Marxistas: Spartacist Publishing Co., New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12435 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Cog: Spartacus Youth League, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12436 (Box 161, Folder 7-8)
  - Educational Outline: Spartacus Youth League, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12437 (Box 161, Folder 9)
  - SYL Internal Discussion Bulletin: Spartacus Youth League, New York, NY, 1975; cuid12438 (Box 161, Folder 10)
  - Paris on the Barricades: Spartacus Youth League of America, New York, NY, 1935; cuid12439 (Box 161, Folder 11)
  - Basic Documents of the Spartacus Youth League: Spartacus Youth Publishing Company, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12440 (Box 161, Folder 12)
  - Spartacus Youth Speakers Bureau: Spartacus Youth Speakers Bureau, New York, NY, 1977; cuid12441 (Box 161, Folder 13)
  - Montana Socialist: State Executive Committee of the Socialist Party, Missoula, MT, 1946; cuid12442 (Box 151, Folder 1, Box 207, Folder 16)
  - How Much Socialism is there in the USA?: Straight Talk Pamphlets, New York, NY, 1978; cuid12443 (Box 161, Folder 14)
  - 1953 SLID Summer Institute Bulletin: Student League for Industrial Democracy, New York, NY, cuid12444 (Box 161, Folder 15)
  - Jensenism: A Closer Look: Students for a Democratic Society, Berkeley, CA, 1973; cuid12445 (Box 161, Folder 16)
  - Join Community Union Newsletter: Students for a Democratic Society, Chigago, IL, 1966; cuid12446 (Box 161, Folder 17)
  - Man and Socialism: Students for a Democratic Society, Chicago, IL, 1967; cuid12447 (Box 161, Folder 18)
  - New Speak: Students for a Democratic Society, Brooklyn, NY, 1967; cuid12448 (Box 161, Folder 19)
  - SDS New Left Notes: Students for a Democratic Society, Chicago, IL, 1968, 1972; cuid12449 (Box 129, Folder 15, Box 206, Folder 7-8)
  - SDS Pamphlet: Students for a Democratic Society, Portage, PA, 1970; cuid12450 (Box 161, Folder 20)
  - Newsletter: Sunrise Books and Press, New York, NY, circa 1970s; cuid12451 (Box 161, Folder 21)
  - Bulletin of Supporters of the International Trotskyist Opposition in the United States: Supporters of the International Trotskyist Opposition, 1993; cuid12452 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - International Discussion Bulletin of the Socialist Workers Party (Britain): SWP International Department/ Socialist Workers Party (Britain), 1977; cuid12453 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - SYL Newsletter: SYL, 1946; cuid12454 (Box 161, Folder 22)
  - OHAL (Oral History of the American Left) Newsletter: Tamiment Library, NYU, New York, NY, 1984; cuid12455 (Box 161, Folder 23)
  - Theory & Practice: A Bulletin of Political Analysis, Discussion, & Information: Theory & Practice, Los Angeles, CA, 1979; cuid12456 (Box 162, Folder 17)
  - Concord: Tolstoy Peace Group, Brooklyn, NY, 1943; cuid12457 (Box 162, Folder 18)
  - Common Sense: Tom Paine Chapter, Young People's Socialist League, Queens, NY, 1972; cuid12458 (Box 162, Folder 19)
  - Advance: Official Newspaper of the Trade Union Action League: Trade Union Action League Birmingham Chapter, Birmingham, AL, 1979-1980; cuid12459 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Amalgamation: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1923; cuid12460 (Box 162, Folder 20)
  - American Company Unions: A Study of Employee Representation Plans, "Works Councils" and Other Substitutes for Labor Unions: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1926; cuid12461 (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - Lenin and the Trade Movement: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, circa 1920s; cuid12462 (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - Lenin: The Great Strategist of the Class War: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1924; cuid12463 (Box 162, Folder 23)
  - Organize the Unorganized: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1926; cuid12464 (Box 162, Folder 24)
  - Revolutionary Crisis of 1918-1921 in Germany, England, Italy and France: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, cuid12465 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Russia in 1924: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, cuid12466 (Box 162, Folder 25)
  - Russian Revolution: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1921; cuid12467 (Box 162, Folder 26)
  - Russian Workers and Workshops in 1926: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, cuid12468 (Box 162, Folder 27)
  - Strike Strategy: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1926; cuid12469 (Box 162, Folder 28)
  - Struggle of the Trade Unions Against Fascism: Trade Union Educational League, Chicago, IL, 1923; cuid12470 (Box 162, Folder 29)
  - Clarte / Bulletin mensuel publie par le cercle clarte: travailleurs de langue francaise aux etats-unis, New York, NY, 1936; cuid12471 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - The Organizer: Twin Cities Industrial Workers of the World, Minneapolis, MN, 2006; cuid12472 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - US GDR Focus: U.S. Committee for Friendship with the German Democratic Republic, New York, NY, 1983-1984, 1987; cuid12473 (Box 163, Folder 3, Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Unity / La Unidad: U.S. League of Revolutionary Struggle / Getting Together Publications, San Francisco, CA/Oakland, CA, 1977-1992; cuid12474 (Box 29, Folder 1-4, Box 41, Folder 2, Box 30, Folder 1-3, Box 42, Box 43, Folder 1-6, Box 113, Folder 1-5, Box 114, Box 115, Box 116, Folder 1-8)
  - Unity: U.S. League of Revolutionary Struggle, Oakland, CA, 1984-1985 (Box 215, Folder 9-10, Box 216, Folder 1-8)